I'm a teacher here in New York City, and I'm really sick of planning out lessons and thinking
about books I'm going to teach and thinking to myself, oh, if I were teaching in Florida right
now, I couldn't teach this lesson. And that's why I'm really excited to share with you all
there's going to be a massive walkout in Florida where thousands of students on April 21st
are going to walk out of school, gain access to a banned history lesson, and enroll in a curriculum
where they can learn history that's not being taught in their school, and register to vote
for people who are going to look out for students' rights. So follow Walk Out to Learn and get
all the details about what's going to happen on April 21st. Because every kid deserves to
learn books like this one in school. So join the thousands of students walking out to learn
on April 21st. Follow Walk Out to Learn.